Narrator: 1
Announcer: The 6:12 train to Poughkeepsie, making stops at Harlem, Beacon,
New Hamburg, and Poughkeepsie is departing from Track 30.
A: That’s our train. Track 30. Come on.
B: OK. Let’s go.
Narrator: 2
A: Excuse me! How far is it to Austin?
B: It’s about forty miles.
A: Thanks a lot.
Narrator: 3
A: Just one more game. Come on!
B: 15–love.
A: Great serve!
Narrator: 4
A: Will all passengers on Delta flight 1182 to Portland
please go to gate sixteen immediately.
B: Gate sixteen. Is that our flight?
C: No, it’s to Portland, Maine, not Portland, Oregon.
Narrator: 5
A: How much is that?
B: Two slices of pizza, a salad, and a soda.
That’s seventeen dollars.
Narrator: 6
A: What’s your address?
B: It’s eighty Park Street.
A: Sorry?
B: Eighty, eight-oh. Park Street.
Narrator: 7
A: OK, be quiet, please.
Open your books to page ninety.
B: What page?
A: Page ninety.